<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data collection protocol on PLAY Project</title>
    <link>/study/protocol/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data collection protocol on PLAY Project</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/study/protocol/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/study/protocol/recruiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/study/protocol/recruiting/</guid>
      <description>Inclusion/Exclusion Criteria Infants&amp;rsquo; natural play in the home is characterized by tremendous variability including variations in: geographic location, climate, socioeconomic status (SES), maternal/paternal employment, childcare experiences, infants’ and mothers’ ages, language environment, physical layout and characteristics of the home, availability of media, toys for play, and so on. Researchers will be able to explore the effects of any/all such factors.
However, to ensure a sufficient sample size and based on conversations with the launch group, we will limit variability along several dimensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/study/protocol/visit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/study/protocol/visit/</guid>
      <description>Home Visit Introduction Say to Mom:
Thanks for letting us come to your home. The visit has a few parts:
I’ll begin by video-recording you and [CHILD] as you go about your day. I will video-record you both for 1 hour. Then, I will ask [CHILD] to play with some toys both by him/herself and with you.
Afterwards, I will ask you some general questions about your family and home, and about [CHILD]’s skills and routines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/study/protocol/visit_prep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/study/protocol/visit_prep/</guid>
      <description> Preparing for Visit Prepare paperwork Write Participant ID on all paperwork (consents and questionnaires). Fill out locomotor milestone worksheet.
Pack equipment  Camera, SD card and extra battery
 Mic Laser Measure Solitary play toy Dyadic play toy Yoga mat Tablet with app for questionnaires (if mom speaks English and/or Spanish, bring both versions of MacArthur), study consent form, Databrary sharing release form, and decibel meter. Answer choice sheet with response scales Participant payment Paper copies of all questionnaires, MCDI, and consent and Databrary forms in case of tablet failure Tools for body dimensions (Height and Weight)- TBD  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/study/protocol/visit_prep.rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/study/protocol/visit_prep.rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>+++ title = “”
date = 2018-12-30T00:00:00 lastmod = 2019-01-07T00:00:00
draft = false # Is this a draft? true/false toc = true # Show table of contents? true/false type = “docs” # Do not modify.
Add menu entry to sidebar. [menu.protocol] name = “Visit Prep” weight = 3 +++
 Preparing for Visit Prepare paperwork Write Participant ID on all paperwork (consents and questionnaires). Fill out locomotor milestone worksheet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>